Total Experience: 4 Year(s) 4 Month(s)

Notice Period: 3 Months

Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Electronics/Telecommunication]

Shital Dinkar Shelukar 🕡 Featured

Controls Engineer - Seeking roles in Software Engineering, Software Developer, Model Based Development, Software Integration, Project Management, Change Management, Defect Management, Requirement Analysis, Application Support, AUTOSAR, Simulink, MATLAB



Current Designation: Senior Software Engineer

Current Company: KPIT Technologies

Current Location: Pune

Pref. Location: Pune, Germany, Bengaluru / Bangalore

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Senior Software Engineer/Developer, Model Development, Software Integration, Project Management, Change Management, Defect Management, Requirement Analysis, Application Support, AUTOSAR, Simulink, MATLAB, C, Stateflow

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Summary

Senior software Developer in model based designing. Model Based development activities including model development and auto-code generation using MATLAB, Simulink, Stateflow. Proficiency in developing application-level software to implement features and functions at a product and system level

3+ years of experience in Core2 architecture, Diesel Engine and MAAB guidelines; Development of SRS (System Requirements Specs), Calibration tuning Guide and Application Guide.

Expertise in tools like MATLAB, Simlunk, Stateflow, Exceed on demand, Clearcase, Winscp, and Integrity Knowledge of CORE2 and AUTOSAR architecture

Basic Knowledge of CAN, LIN or other communication protocols used in automotive

3+ years of experience in creating a working software for OEMs following Emission in building program specific builds (consisting of the entire Aftertreatment system and models) and testing them.

Smart sensor datalink calibration tuning

Work Experience

KPIT Technologies Ltd. as Technical Lead Aug 2016 to Jan 2021

KPIT Technologies as Senior Software Engineer Aug 2016 to Till Date

Project: Value Package Integration (VPI)

Client

Cummins India Limited (Pune)

Environment Development

Role

Senior Team Member

Description:

? The primary objective of VPI control team is to develop and test Aftertreatment Functionality using Model Based Techniques and MATLAB to meet the Norms requirement to regulate the emissions

? Worked as a software developer and tester in CES (Cummins Emission Solutions: Aftertreatment Controls) which focuses on reducing the emissions emitted from Tractors, Trucks and Cars in order to meet the Emission norms

- ? Understand Customer requirements and translate into systems requirement
- ? Responsible for build integration and release for different platform.
- ? Manage the definition, communication and resolution of issues with internal, onsite team, customer.
- ? Code Coverage verification and validation by checking code coverage of developed models against the requirements.
- ? Test new developed algorithms in MATLAB Simulink and on Test Bench using MIL ,SIL, Trace 32 and Calterm 3 and 4.
- ? Creation of traceability matrix and Test vectors on developed model considering MCDC coverage of the functionality of the model.
- ? Responsible for review like Evaluation, Implementation, SRS, Application guide and testing part as well
- ? Functional verification and validation of developed models against the requirements.

KPIT Technologies Ltd. as Technical Lead Aug 2016 to Aug 2016

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Electronics/Telecommunication) from Mitaoe, Pune in 2016

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

Polytechnique

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
Simulink, Stateflow, MATLAB, AUTOSAR			

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Marathi				

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No Job Type: Permanent / Temporary

Employment Status: Full Time, Part Time